Why'd you stop?
لِمَ توقفت؟
It's the Booth House.
.(إنه منزل (آل بوث
You know, a family used to live here a while back, right?
تعلم، العائلة التي كانت تقطن هنا منذ فترة طويلة، اليس كذلك؟
Yeah, I heard they went missing.
.اجل، سمعت إنه اختفوا
Because of the curse.
.بسبب اللعنة
What curse?
أي لعنة؟
A witch used to live here, man. Now this place is cursed.
.اعتادت ساحرة ان تعيش هنا يا صاح .الآن المكان ملعون
Wait, you haven't heard about this?
،مهلاً ألم تسمع عن ذلك؟
Well, she and her daughter lived here when this place was first built.
حسناً، هي وإبنتها .سكنا هنا عندما بُنيَ هذا المكان
When her daughter died, she was blamed for it.
،عندما ماتت إبنتها .ألقى الناس اللوم عليها
They say, she locked herself in the basement,
،يُقال إنها حبست نفسها في القبو
and eventually, she killed herself.
.وفي النهاية قتلت نفسها
Dude, no. That's not even close to what I heard.
.يا صاح، لا .ليس هذا حتى اقرب لما سمعته
I heard the guy who used to live here, Mr. Booth, was a monster.
سمعت إن الرجل الذي كان يقطن .السيد (بوث) كان وحشاً
He went crazy, killed his whole family,
،جنَّ جنونه،قتل عائلته
and then shot himself.
.ومن ثمَّ إنتحر
Yeah, but what about the bodies? The bodies were never found.
اجل، لكن ماذا عن الجثث؟ لم يُعثر عليها قط
They say, he hid the bodies somewhere inside the house,
،يُقال إنه خبأ الجثث في مكان ما في المنزل
that's why their ghosts are stuck here.
.لذلك السبب أشباحهم عالقة هناك
I guess no one really knows, then.
.اعتقد إن لا احد يعرف حق المعرفة اذن
Yeah.
.اجل
Dude, it's late. We should go.
.يا صاح الوقت متأخر، لنمضِ
Where are you going?
الى اين تذهب؟
Dude, what are you doing?
يا صاح، ماذا تفعل؟
What is wrong with you?
ما خطبك؟
Why you're always such a wuss?
لِمَ انت جبان دوماً؟
You always say you want to do something scary,
،لطالما قلت إنك تريد القيام بأمر جنوني
but only when it's made up.
.فقط عندما يكون من صنعنا
- Shut up. - Gosh...
.إخرس- ...يا إلهي-
Dude, up there!
!يا صاح، في الأعلى
What?
ماذا؟
Let's get out of here!
!لنرحل من هنا
Every house has a story.
"لكل منزل قصة"
A story that lives inside it,
"قصة تسكنه"
like a memory in a brain.
".كالذاكرة في الذهن"
The characters of these stories are the ghosts
"شخصيات هذه القصة أشباح"
of the people who once inhabited these places.
".الناس الذين سكنوا هذه الأماكن ذات مرة"
Who lived out their narratives only to forget
"الذين عاشوا رواياتهم فقط لينسوها"
and be forgotten by the passage of time.
"وتغيب عن الأذهان بمرور الوقت"
But in some places, these stories are never quite finished,
"،لكن في بعض الأماكن" "تلك القصص لم تكتمل تماماً"
leaving the spirits to wander aimlessly like a spinning wheel.
"تاركة الأرواح تتجول بلا هدف كعجلة دوارة"
And I think...
...وأعتقد
that's what's been going on at the Booth House
(ذلك ما كان يجري في منزل (بوث
for the last 30 years.
.خلال الـ30 عاماً الماضية
The horrors that happened to the missing family have been buried here,
،الفظائع التي حلت بتلك العائلة دُفِنت هنا
hidden in the darkness behind closed doors.
.مخفية في الظلمة وراء ابواب مسدودة
I think there's a story here, waiting to be told.
،اعتقد إن قصة هنا .تنتظر السرد
And that's why I'm here.
.ولهذا السبب انا هنا
Welcome back!
!اهلا بكم مجدداً
You're listening to 94.9,
انتم تستمعون الى التردد 94.9
Witching Season Radio!
!راديو موسم السحر
Midnight is here, you know what that means?
،منتصف الليل هنا هل تعرفون ما يعني ذلك؟
Halloween is officially upon us!
!حل علينا عيد القديسين رسمياً
The veil is thin and the world of the dead and living
الحجاب رقيق والعالم بين الموتى والأحياء
are almost interchangeable.
"قابل للتبديل تقريباً"
To celebrate, stick with me
للإحتفال، إبقوا معي
as we broadcast for the next 24 hours.
.حيث سيستمر بثنا للـ24 ساعة القادمة
Hello?
مرحباً؟
I'm here at the, the Booth House.
.(انا عند منزل (بوث
This place is exactly as I pictured it would be.
.المكان تماماً كما تخيّلته
Doesn't look like anyone is here.
.لا يبدو إن اي احد هنا
Everything is covered in sheets.
.كل شيء مغطى بالملاءات
It's a locked door.
.إنه باب مقفول
Maybe it leads to the basement?
ربما يؤدي الى القبو
Hello?
مرحباً؟
Jesus.
.يا إلهي
I found the study.
.وجدت المكتب
And a really nice writing desk.
.وطاولة كتابة جميلة
And of course I already broke something so, there's that.
.وبالطبع كسرت شيئاً بالفعل
- God, Dani! - Dad!
!(رباه (داني- !ابي-
What's your problem?
ما مشكلتك؟
I thought you were asleep.
.خلتكِ نائمة
- You alright? - Yeah, I'm okay.
هل انتِ بخير؟- .اجل، انا بخير-
What the hell?
ما هذا؟
Watch your mouth.
.انتبهي لألفاظكِ
You say it all the time.
.تقولها على الدوام
So I thought someone was meeting us here?
إذاً، اعتقد إن احداً سيقابلنا هنا؟
You know, uh...
...تعلم
you don't even worry about it, we're good to go.
،لا تقلقي حتى بشأن ذلك .جاهزان للرحيل
Where the hell is the thermostat?
أين منظم الحرارة بحق الجحيم؟
Watch your mouth.
.إنتبهي لألفاظكِ
So what's in there?
ماذا هناك، إذن؟
Oh, uh, ghosts.
.أشباح
There're ghosts?
توجد أشباح؟
No.
.كلا
They're the friendly ghosts, okay?
إنها أشباح ودودة، إتفقنا؟
So, so, they're like the...
...لذا إنها اشبه بـ
what's that dumb... like, they're like the Casper,
،ما أسم ذلك الغبي ،"مثل "كاسبر
they're, they're friendly, they're not going to, they're not going to...
.إنها ودودة، لن تقوم، لن تقوم
There's no ghosts, alright? I'm...
...لا توجد أشباح، مفهوم؟
So...
....لذا
I was... it was just a...
...كنت فقط
God, damn it.
.اللعنة
Wow.
.عجباً
Looks like the one Grandma and Grandpa gave us.
.يبدو كالذي اعطاه الجدان لنا
Dad.
.ابي
No. Stop it!
!لا أوقفه
When that school bell rings tomorrow at 2:30,
،عندما يدق جرس المدرسة غداً في الـ2:30"
- officially Halloween has begun. - Alright, here we go.
."بدأ عيد القديسين بالفعل" .وها نحن اولاء
This year, with Halloween landing...
"....هذه السنة مع بداية عيد القديسين"
I don't want to watch TV.
.لا اريد التفرج على التلفاز
- ...officials have urged... - Why?
لماذا؟
They always have the best stuff on in October.
.لديهم افضل البرامج خلال شهر اكتوبر
- ...children. This is... - Hey folks, come on down
"يا قوم تعالوا"
There's still plenty of time to pick up
"لا يزال هناك الكثير من الوقت لإختيار"
your Halloween Jack O'Lantern!
"جاك اولانتيرن الخاص بك"
And, of course, if you stay after dark,
،وبالطبع ان بقيت لما بعد الظلام"
the corn maze becomes the "Haunted Corn Maze."
متاهة حقل الذرة تصبح "متاهة حقل الذرة المسكونة"
Hey, where do you want me to come out from?
من اين تريد ان تخرج؟
- Uh, just... - They super glued the coffin lid up.
"لقد أحكموا اغلاق النعش"
See?
أترى؟
- Here? - No, no, no, other side of the coffin.
من هنا؟ لا، لا، من الجانب الأخر من النعش
Yeah, but, I'll knock shit over if I come out here.
.اجل، سأبرحكَ ضرباً ان خرجت من هناك
- No, the right... Your right side of the coffin. - Oh, here?
.لا، اليمين، يمينك من النعش من هنا؟
- Yes. - Okay, got it.
اجل .حسناً
- This is lame. - Welcome everyone
.هذا ممل .اهلاً بالجميع
to "Count Spookula's Horrific...
"الكونت سبوكولا هورفيك"
- It's not lame, it's Spookula. - ...Spookula...
."إنه ليس ممل  إنه "سبوكولا- "..سبوكولا"-
- ...be your host tonight... - He is lame.
..سيكون مضيفكم الليلة .إنه ممل
...and take you through a journey...
...ويأخذكم بمغامرة
Ah, come on, he is great.
.بحقك، إنه رائع
I, I grew up watching this, okay?
كبرت وأنا اشاهده، إتفقنا؟
- Me and your mo... - We've got professional,
،انا وأمـ .لدينا محترفون
we've got semi-professional,
.ولدينا شبه محترفون
- and we've got... - It's Spookula.
...ولدينا ."إنه "سبوكولا
It's, it's not bad.
.ليس سيئاً
...Todd made last week.
"،قام تود الأسبوع الماضي"
Okay, Count, just, just stick to the script, okay?
حسناً يا كونت، إلتزم بالنص، إتفقنا؟
- What are we doing here? - You told me to promote local films,
ماذا نفعل هنا؟
Came for work, sweetie. You know that.
.اتيت للعمل عزيزتي، تعلمين ذلك
But why here?
لكن لِمَ هنا؟
In this house.
.في هذا المنزل
You know, sometimes it's...
....تعلمين، احياناً
Sometimes it's hard for...
...احياناً من الصعب
for people to...
...على الناس ان
for me, to be creative.
.صعب علي، ان اكون مبدعاً
And I guess that's everyone, it's hard,
،واعتقد إن ذلك حال الجميع ،من الصعب
it's hard for anyone to be creative...
...على كل واحد ان يكون مبدعاً
after something bad has happened.
.بعد حصول مكروه له
I find that, uh...
..اجد ذلك
that sometimes a change of scenery,
،احياناً تغيير المشهد
doing something new, can help.
.فعل شيء جديد، ينفع
And I guess I figured that it would be good for me.
.وأرتأيت ان ذلك سيفيدني
I mean...
...اعني
good for us.
.يفيدنا
With everything that's going on.
.مع كل ما يجري
Sweetheart, I know that...
...عزيزتي، اعرف إن ذلك
I know this isn't what you want.
.اعرف ان ذلك ليس ما تبتغينه
Maybe when we're done though, I... we can go camping or something?
...ربما عندما ننتهي يمكننا ان نذهب للتخييم او ما شابه؟
Really?
حقاً؟
Yeah.
.اجل
Go up to the lake?
نذهب للبحيرة؟
- Yes! - Yeah? Okay.
!اجل اجل؟، حسناً
Done.
.إتفقنا
Are you okay here for a minute? I got to make a phone call.
هل ستكوني بخير هنا لدقيقة؟ .اريد ان اتصل
- Mm-hmm. - Okay, I'll be back, alright? There you go.
.حسناً، سأعود بعد قليل إتفقنا؟، ها انت ذا
Yeah, hi. Uh, it's me, um...
...اجل، مرحباً، إنه انا
I just wanted to let you know I'm here.
.اردت فقط ان احيطك علماً إننا هنا
Uh, we...
....نحن
Welcome back, boils and ghouls,
،مرحباً بكم مجدداً يا اولاد ويا فتيات
to the channel 33,
،في القناة 33
- Halloween Spookathon! - So we just came in...
!"في مهرجان "سبوكوثون للهالوين ...أتينا للتو
...and I hope that's fine.
.وأمل ان يكون لديكم مانع
I, I didn't know what else to do, so...
...لم اعرف ما افعل غير ذلك
Yeah, if we see you...
....اجل، إن رأيناك
great, uh, but, yeah, just figured I'd let you know we're here. So...
.عظيم، اجل ...ارتأيت ان اخبرك إنني هنا لذا
Yeah.
.اجل
Who's there?
من هناك؟
You found her.
.لقد وجدتها
What?
ماذا؟
Cynthia?
سينثيا)؟)
Isn't she beautiful?
أليست جميلة؟
Wha... what are you doing here?
ماذا تفعلين هنا؟
I've always been here.
.لطالما كنت هنا
You're not real.
.لستِ حقيقية
I know you're stuck.
.اعرف إنك عالق
I jus... just don't have anything left.
.لم يتبقَ عندي شيء
Don't have any ideas, any...
....ليست لدي اي افكار، اي
inspiration, anything.
.إلهام، أي شيء
I'm, I'm just going in a circle.
.انا في دوّامة
I'm so sorry.
.آسف حقاً
Sorry I was always gone.
.آسف على رحيلي دوماً
I should've been there for you.
.كان يجب ان اكون حاضراً لأجلك
And I know I wasn't.
.أعلم إنني لم اكن موجود
Please. Please don't go.
.ارجوكِ، لا تذهبي
Please, please, please, please stay.
.ارجوكِ، ارجوكِ، ارجوكِ، أبقي
I can't stay.
.لا أستطيع البقاء
- I can't. - Why?
.لا استطيع- لماذا؟-
But I can help you.
.لكن يمكنني مساعدتك
What?
ماذا؟
I know what you're looking for.
.اعرف عمَّ تبحث
It's in this house.
.إنه في هذا المنزل
What? What's in this house?
ماذا؟، ماذا في هذا المنزل؟
Keep looking.
.إستمر بالبحث
You'll find it.
.ستجده
It's right in front of you.
.إنه امام عينك
Hello?
مرحباً؟
My car broke down
.سيارتي تعطلت
and I have a party to get to, so,
،ولدي حفلة لأحضرها، لذا
I was wondering if you could
كنت اتساءل ان كان بمقدورك
maybe help me?
ربما مساعدتي؟
Hello?
مرحباً؟
Hello!
!مرحباً
She looks down and realizes her daughter is gone.
.نظرت وأدركت إن ابنتها اختفت
Something is watching her.
.شيء يراقبها
Masked killer.
.قاتل مقنع
Please! Please, help me!
!ارجوك، ساعدني
...of a Halloween mask.
.من قناع هالووين
Uh, the local authorities...
...السلطات المحلية
Oh, God, please, he is coming!
!يا إلهي، ارجوك، إنه قادم
...to please remain inside your homes...
...ان تلازموا بيوتكم
Oh, my God, please!
!يا إلهي، ارجوك
...suspicious activities or sightings
نشاطات مشبوهة
during this incredibly dangerous situation.
.خلال هذا الوضع الخطر
There is a killer on the loose.
.هناك قاتل طليق
Oh, please! Please!
!ارجوك، ارجوك
Please, don't kill me.
.ارجوك، لا تقتلني
I, I don't want to die.
.لا اريد الموت
Don't do that.
.لا تفعل ذلك
Knife to meet you.
.سكين يرحب بك
It's a fucking shit!
!إنه هراء
Dad. Dad!
!ابي، ابي
Dad!
!ابي
Can we go trick or treating tonight?
هل يمكننا القيام بالخدعة ام الحلوى الليلة؟
Dani, I didn't get any sleep last night,
.لم أنم الليلة الماضية أبداً يا (داني)
and I didn't get any work done.
.ولم انجز أي عمل
Probably not, no.
.على الأرجح كلا
Mom always took me trick or treating.
.لطالما أخذتني والدتي للقيام بالخدعة أم الحلوى
Mom is not here!
!أمكِ ليست هنا
I'm sorry.
.أنا آسف
Dani, I'm sorry. Okay? I'm sorry.
.أنا آسفٌ يا (داني) .حسناً؟ أنا آسف
I love you and...
...أنا أحبكِ و
I'm doing the best that I can.
.أنا أبذل قصارى جهدي
Okay, look.
.حسناً، انظري
I have a lot of work to get done still, okay?
لا يزال لدي الكثير من العمل لأنجزه حسناً؟
But, let me get through that,
لكن، دعيني اتخطى ذلك
and let's see if we can find something
ودعينا نرى إذا ما كان بإمكاننا إيجاد شيءٍ ما
that might work as a costume.
.قد ينفع كزي
- Really? - Yeah.
حقاً؟ - .أجل -
Again, it's going to take me a little bit,
مرةً أخرى، سيستغرق الأمر مني بعض الشيء
I got to play catchup, but, just...
عليّ أن انجز عملي بسرعة ...فقط
find something and we'll, we'll go.
.اعثري على شيءٍ ما، وسوف نذهب
Scarecrow.
.فزاعة
Please help! Help, please help me!
!الرجاء المساعدة !النجدة، من فضلكم ساعدوني
Shit!
!سحقاً
Hey, Dani?
يا (داني)؟
Were you upstairs?
هل كنتِ في الطابق العلوي؟
What you doing?
ما الذي تفعلينه؟
I'm coloring.
.اقوم بالتلوين
Do you want to go outside?
هل تودينَ الذهاب للخارج؟
Sure.
.بالطبع
Okay.
.حسناً
Look at this here.
.انظري إلى هذا هنا
Yeah, see? Like a, like a spooky ghost, right?
انظري، اترين؟ مثل شبحٍ مخيف اليس كذلك؟
Um... I can't see anything.
.لا يمكنني رؤية أي شيء
Uh... Alright, I got to go finish my work.
.حسناً، يجب أن اذهب لإنهاء عملي
Just give me, like, 45 minutes? Deal?
فقط امنحيني 45 دقيقة اتفقنا؟
Okay, you want to hold onto this?
حسناً، هل تودينَ الإمساك بهذا؟
Just give me a little bit of time, okay?
فقط امنحيني القليل من الوقت اتفقنا؟
But you promised me funnel cake!
!لكنكِ وعدتِني بكعكة الفونيل
Oh, look at this, you're such a peach,
انظر إلى هذا يا لك من شخص
you waited for me.
.لقد انتظرتني
Who did this to you?
من فعل هذا بك؟
Did you see where they went?
هل رأيت إلى أين ذهبوا؟
She's still here.
.إنها لا تزال هنا
Where?
أين؟
Where is she?
أين هي؟
What are you going to do?
ما الذي ستفعله؟
Are you going to chop me?
هل ستقوم بتقطيعي؟
Hey.
.مرحباً
I'm really sorry, okay?
أنا آسفٌ حقاً، حسناً؟
I'm...
...أنا
- I was almost... - You're a liar!
...كنت على وشك - !أنت كاذب -
I, I'm not...
...أنا، أنا لستُ
I didn't lie, okay?
أنا لم أكذب، حسناً؟
I just got distracted, I was just trying to finish so I could just be done.
لقد تم تشتيت إنتباهي، لقد كنت أحاول .أن أنتهي حتى أنجز العمل
You don't listen to me.
.أنت لا تستمع إلي
I liste... Dani.
.أنا استمع... (داني)
Okay, I'm just trying to get this done.
.حسناً، أنا فقط أحاول إنجاز العمل
That's, that's why we're here, right?
لهذا السبب نحنُ هنا، أليس كذلك؟
I ca... I have to focus on other things sometimes,
لا بد لي من التركيز على أشياء أخرى في بعض الأحيان
and I'm sorry I got distracted.
.وأنا آسفٌ لأنني تشتت إنتباهي
You don't care about me.
.أنت لا تكترث لأمري
I don't even care about you? Really?
أنا لا أكترث لأمركِ حتى؟ حقاً؟
What do I spend my days doing Dani? Huh?
بماذا اقضي أيامي فاعلاً يا (داني)؟
I spend my days carrying you from one spot to another,
اقضي أيامي في نقلكِ من مكانٍ إلى آخر
cooking for you, feeding you.
اطبخ من أجلكِ اطعمكِ
Do you realize that you're not the only one who lost her?
هل تدركينَ أنكِ لستِ الوحيدة التي فقدتِها؟
Like, does that even occur to you?
مثل، هل هذا يحدث لك حتى؟
That maybe you're the reason she's gone.
.ربما أنتِ سبب رحيلها
And now I'm the one who gets to carry you around,
والآن أنا من يحمل العبء
I'm the one who gets to clean you and dress you,
أنا من يقوم بتنظيفكِ ويلبسكِ ملابسكِ
and take care of you all day!
!ويعتني بكِ طوال اليوم
I'm sorry.
.أنا آسفة
No. I'm sorry.
.كلا، أنا آسف
Okay? I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
.حسناً؟ أنا آسف، أنا آسف
This is me. This is on me. Not you.
هذا أنا، العبء يقع علي .ليس عليكِ
The shortcomings we have as a family are not your fault.
العيوب التي لدينا كعائلة .ليست خطأكِ
It's my failure as your dad.
.إنه فشلي كوالدكِ
All of this was...
...كل هذا كان
just me trying and, like usually,
أنا فقط أقوم بالمحاولة وكالعادة
I couldn't do it right.
.لم أستطع فعل ذلك بشكلٍ صحيح
Okay? I love you, Dani, so much and I'm, I'm sorry for...
حسناً؟ أحبكِ يا (داني) كثيراً ...وأنا آسفٌ على
for what I put you through.
.على ما وضعتكِ فيه
This place...
...هذا المكان
it's not good for us.
.إنه ليس جيداً بالنسبة لنا
It's just time we go home.
.لقد حان الوقت للعودة إلى المنزل
Are you okay?
هل أنتِ بخير؟
I got to go pee.
.يجب أن أذهب للتبول
Hey, Dani.
.يا (داني)
- Dani. - What?
.(داني) - ماذا؟ -
Hey, you almost done?
هل شارفتِ على الإنتهاء؟
In a minute.
.في غضون دقيقة
Okay. I'll be ready in just a few minutes, okay?
حسناً، سأكون جاهزاً خلال دقائق قليلة حسناً؟
Okay.
.حسناً
I know what you're looking for.
.أعلم ما الذي تبحث عنه
It's in this house.
.إنه في هذا المنزل
Jesus.
.يا إلهي
Dani?
(داني)؟
Dani!
!(داني)
Dani.
.(داني)
Every house has a story.
"لكل منزل قصة"
A story that lives inside it,
"قصة تسكنه"
like a memory in a brain.
".كالذاكرة في الذهن"
The characters of these stories are the ghosts
"شخصيات هذه القصة أشباح"
of the people who once inhabited this places.
".الناس الذين سكنوا هذه الأماكن ذات مرة"
Who lived out their narratives only to forget
"الذين عاشوا رواياتهم فقط لينسوها"
and be forgotten by the passage of time.
"وتغيب عن الأذهان بمرور الوقت"
But in some places, these stories are never quite finished,
"،لكن في بعض الأماكن" "نلك القصص لم تكتمل تماماً"
leaving the spirits to wander aimlessly like a spinning wheel.
"تاركة الأرواح تتجول بلا هدف كعجلة دوارة"
And I think...
...وأعتقد
that's what's been going on at the Booth House
(ذلك ما كان يجري في منزل (بوث
for the last 30 years.
.خلال الـ30 عاماً الماضية
The horrors that happened to the missing family
الفظائع التي حلت بتلك العائلة المفقودة
have been buried here,
دفنت هنا
hidden in the darkness behind closed doors.
.مخفية في الظلمة وراء ابواب مسدودة
I think there's a story here, waiting to be told.
،اعتقد إن قصة هنا .تنتظر السرد
Oh, shit!
!سحقاً
Is this a dream?
هل هذا حلم؟
It has to be a dream.
.لا بد وأن يكون حلماً
Ho... how do I wake up?
كيف استيقظت؟
Does this feel like a dream?
هل هذا يشبه الحلم؟
This can't be real.
.لا يمكن أن يكون هذا حقيقياً
None of this, it can't be real, it just...
لا شيء من هذا، لا يمكن أن يكون حقيقياً ...إنه فقط
How do I wake up?
كيف استيقظت؟
This is still your story.
.لا تزال هذه قصتك
You've got to finish what you've started.
.عليك أن تنهي ما بدأته
There is no story.
.لا توجد هنالك قصة
I lost her.
.لقد فقدتها
I can't get out, I don't know how to get out.
لا يمكنني الخروج .لا أعرف كيف أخرج
I don't know where to go.
.لا أعرف إلى أين أذهب
I lost Dani.
.لقد فقدت (داني)
I lost Dani. I don't know, I've looked everywhere.
لقد فقدت (داني)، لا أعرف .لقد بحثت في كل مكان
What happened here?
ما الذي حدث هنا؟
Welcome back.
.مرحباً بعودتك
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
She's not here.
.إنها ليست هنا
- Who? - Who you think?
من؟ - من تعتقد؟ -
Little one, the girl, Dani.
.الصغيرة، الفتاة، (داني)
How do you know her name?
كيف تعرف إسمها؟
Do you ever get tired of doing the same thing
هل سئمت يوماً من فعل نفس الشيء
over and over and over?
مراراً وتكراراً؟
Where is she?
أين هي؟
- She took her. - Who?
.لقد أخذتها - من؟ -
Who took her?
من أخذتها؟
The bitch from your story.
.العاهرة من قصتك
The one who always gets away over again.
.التي تنجو بفعلتها في كل مرة دائماً
Where are they?
أين هم؟
That's, that's pretty funny.
.هذا مضحكٌ جداً
Where?
أين؟
Well...
...حسناً
I guess it's time for you to die again.
أعتقد أنه حان الوقت لكي تموت .مرةً أخرى
Jesus Christ!
!يا يسوع المسيح
Dani!
!(داني)
No, no, no, no, no...
...كلا، كلا، كلا، كلا
God. Listen.
.يا إلهي، انصتي
You found her.
.لقد وجدتها
What?
ماذا؟
Isn't she beautiful?
اليست جميلة؟
You.
.أنتِ
You did this.
.أنتِ فعلتِ هذا
Yeah.
.أجل
Now, now you're free.
.أنت حرٌ الآن
No.
.كلا
No, don't, don't be upset. No, I did this for us.
.كلا، إياك، لا تنزعج .كلا، لقد فعلت هذا من أجلنا
Oh, it's okay.
.لا بأس
No, it's okay.
.كلا، لا بأس
It's okay, it's okay.
.لا بأس، لا بأس
It's okay.
.لا بأس
Jesus Christ.
.يا يسوع المسيح
911 emergency.
.هنا الطواريء
Hello?
مرحباً؟
Is there someone on the line?
هل هنالك شخصٌ ما على الخط؟
They're both dead.
.كلاهما قد مات
Who is dead, sir?
من الميت يا سيدي؟
Yes, they're, they're both dead. I...
أجل، كلاهما ميت ...أنا
Okay, sir. I'm going to need you to answer some questions.
حسناً سيدي، سأحتاج منك الإجابة .على بعض الأسئلة
Can you start from the beginning?
هل يمكنك أن تبدأ من البداية؟
The beginning?
من البداية؟
I was away.
.كنتُ مسافراً
For work, on a trip.
.من أجل العمل، في رحلة
Try... trying to... trying to finish my story.
.محاولاً إنهاء قصتي
I left Dani alone with Cynthia.
.تركت (داني) وحدها مع (سينثيا)
I should... should've, should've been there.
...كان يجب .كان يجب أن أكون هناك
Shou... should've been there for both of them.
.كان يجب أن أكون هناك من أجلهما
When I came home...
...عندما عدتُ للمنزل
I found Dani dead.
.وجدتُ (داني) ميتة
Cynthia drowned her in the tub.
.اغرقتها (سينثيا) في الحوض
Cynthia...
...(سينثيا)
So I came down the downstairs...
...لذلك نزلتُ إلى الطابق السفلي
and I stabbed her to death.
.وطعنتها حتى الموت
I just stabbed her...
...لقد طعنتها للتو
Every house has a story.
"لكل منزل قصة"
A story that lives inside it,
"قصة تسكنه"
like a memory in a brain.
".كالذاكرة في الذهن"
The characters of these stories are the ghosts
"شخصيات هذه القصة أشباح"
of the people who once inhabited these places.
".الناس الذين سكنوا هذه الأماكن ذات مرة"
Who lived out their narratives only to forget
"الذين عاشوا رواياتهم فقط لينسوها"
and be forgotten by the passage of time.
"وتغيب عن الأذهان بمرور الوقت"
But in some places, these stories are never quite finished,
"،لكن في بعض الأماكن" "تلك القصص لم تكتمل تماماً"
leaving the spirits to wander aimlessly like a spinning wheel.
"تاركة الأرواح تتجول بلا هدف كعجلة دوارة"
And I think...
...وأعتقد
that's what's been going on at the Booth House
(ذلك ما كان يجري في منزل (بوث
for the last 30 years.
.خلال الـ30 عاماً الماضية
The horrors that happened to the missing family
،الفظائع التي حلت بتلك العائلة
have been buried here,
دُفِنت هنا
hidden in the darkness behind closed doors.
.مخفية في الظلمة وراء ابواب مسدودة
I think there's a story here, waiting to be told.
،اعتقد إن قصة هنا .تنتظر السرد
And that's why I'm here.
.ولهذا السبب أنا هنا